Faculty Women's Club. Executive Board. Minutes of meetings. 1918-2000.
UCLA Library Special Collections
Faculty Women's Club. Executive Board. Minutes of meetings.
1918-2000
University Archives Record Series 78
UCLA Library Special Collections
1.6 linear ft. (4 boxes)
Record Series 78 contains the minutes of meetings held by the Executive Board of UCLA's Faculty Women's Club. Files also include agendas from 1942-1943 and 1969-1970.
Faculty Women's Club.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Scope and Content
Record Series 78 contains the minutes of meetings held by the Executive Board of UCLA's Faculty Women's Club. Files also include agendas from 1942-1943 and 1969-1970.
This is an active record series; additional University records are expected to be added.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 3521009
- Minutes., 1918-1921. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1932-1933. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  General note
  Officer: Elizabeth Klingberg.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1933-1934. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Officer: Florence A. Wilson.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1934-1935. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Officer: Bertha Haines.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1935-1936. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Officer: Effie Shambaugh.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1936-1937. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Officers: Mary Upham/Sarah Adsatt.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1937-1938. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Officer: Maria Lopez de Lowther.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1938-1939. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Officer: Eleanor H. Johnson.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1939-1940. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Officer: Kate Gordon Moore.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1940-1941. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Officer: Maude R. Murdoch.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1941-1942. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Officer: Clara Humphrey.
- Executive board - agenda of meetings., 1942-1943. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Officer: Daphne H. Daus.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1942-1943. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1943-1944. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Officer: Margaret Carhart.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1944-1945. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Officers: Louise C. Anderson/Katherine McLaughlin.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1945-1946. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Officer: Bernice Hooper.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1946-1947. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Officer: Emma Skillman Stone.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings, 1947-1948. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Officer: Hansena Fredericksom.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1948-1949. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Officer: Alice Moreman.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1949-1950. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Officer: Gertrude T. Huberty.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1950-1951. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Officer: Dorothy Robbins.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1951-1952. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Officer: Archine Fetty.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1952-1953. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Officer: Hazel Hoel.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1953-1954. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Officer: Betty Stacks.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1954-1955. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Officer: Viola L. Warren.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1955-1956. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Officer: Evelyn Hodgson.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1956-1957. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Officer: Joyce S. Nelson.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1957-1958. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Officer: Carmela Speroni.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1958-1959. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Officer: Ann Sumner.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1959-1960. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Officer: Lillian Asimow.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1960-1961. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Officer: Brownie Pucket.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1961-1962. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Officer: Grace Handy.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1962-1963. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Officer: Helen B. Boelter.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1963-1964. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Officer: Jeanne Durham.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1964-1965. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Officer: Louise York.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1965-1966. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Officer: Janice Hamilton.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1966-1967. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Officer: Nancy Leondes.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1967-1968. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Officer: Mary Erickson.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1968-1969. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Officer: Pat Hardwick.
- Executive board - agenda of meetings., 1969-1970. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Officer: Barbara Comrey.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1969-1970. (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folders 13-14)
  Officer: Sylvia Winstein.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1972-1973. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Officer: Penny Hutchinson.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1973-1974. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Officer: Joanne Knopoff.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings, 1974-1975. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Officer: Barbara La Force.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1975-1976. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Officer: Audrey Marrocco.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1976-1977. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Officer: Eva Orbach.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1977-1978. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Officer: Bee Welmers.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1978-1979. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Officer: Pat Nagy.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings, 1979-1980. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Officer: Sonny Harris.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1980-1981. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Officer: Dianne Homsher.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1981-1982. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Officer: Sandy Spolsky.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1982-1983. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Officer: Jane Jones. No min 83/84, 84/85.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1985-1986. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Officer: Helen Nefkens. No min 83/84, 84/85.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1986-1987. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Officer: Berg Eldred.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1987-1988. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Officer: Jean Serafetinides. No mins 88/89, 89/90, 90/91.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1988-1989. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Officer: Ida Friedlander.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1990-1991. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Officer: Elaine Wise.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings, 1991-1992. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Officer: Elizabeth Cecchetti. No mins 92/93.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1992-1993. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Officer: Mildred Massey.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1993-1994. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Officer: Ann Sprowls.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1994-1995. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Officer: Diana Hawthorne.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1995-1996. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Officer: Marinette Kubeck.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1996-1997. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Officer: Yolaine Dauphine.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1997-1998. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Officer: Felicite Halma.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1998-1999. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Officer: Sari Halasz.
- Executive board - minutes of meetings., 1999-2000. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Officer: Margaret Churchill.